<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-25T13:20:45-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">devblog</title><subtitle>Development Blog for Art, Games and Personal Stuff</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Getting Bootstrap To Work With Jekyll On Github Pages</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/bootstrap/2018/12/18/Getting-Bootstrap-to-Work-with-Jekyll-on-GitHub-Pages.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Getting Bootstrap To Work With Jekyll On Github Pages" /><published>2018-12-18T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-12-18T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/bootstrap/2018/12/18/Getting-Bootstrap-to-Work-with-Jekyll-on-GitHub-Pages</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/bootstrap/2018/12/18/Getting-Bootstrap-to-Work-with-Jekyll-on-GitHub-Pages.html">&lt;p&gt;When I learned front-end web development, I was introduced to Bootstrap and how easy it is to create quickly a responsive website. I knew from the beginning, if I were to make any blog or site, it will be using the framework for easy responsive design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn’t want to take long figuring out the CSS to make a responsive site from scratch. I don’t really care that it looks like vanilla Bootstrap. I just want the site to work, and I wanted it done quickly. Problem was, Bootstrap doesn’t work out the box with Jekyll while hosted by GitHub Pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I attempted a few step by step or guides on how to get it working, but they ultimately didn’t work out. I thought I wouldn’t be able to use GitHub Pages, and tried deploying to Netlify, but the deployment kept failing for some reason and I never got it up. So I continued to look for a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I eventually came upon a &lt;a href=&quot;https://simpleit.rocks/ruby/jekyll/tutorials/how-to-add-bootstrap-4-to-jekyll-the-right-way/&quot;&gt;guide&lt;/a&gt; that claimed it was showing you how to do it the “right way.” For me, the guide was manageable. It’s probably not a guide for absolute beginners who aren’t familiar with command line or Jekyll. But it got the job done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy to see I got Jekyll to work with Bootstrap and also running online. Simple layout and styling for now. Nothing customized just yet. Just gonna use vanilla styling. But will change the layout at least to accommodate content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Progress!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ohaeboy</name></author><summary type="html">When I learned front-end web development, I was introduced to Bootstrap and how easy it is to create quickly a responsive website. I knew from the beginning, if I were to make any blog or site, it will be using the framework for easy responsive design.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Beginnings: Creating The Devblog With Jekyll</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/2018/12/16/New-Beginnings-Creating-the-Devblog-with-Jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Beginnings: Creating The Devblog With Jekyll" /><published>2018-12-16T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2018-12-16T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/2018/12/16/New-Beginnings:-Creating-the-Devblog-with-Jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/2018/12/16/New-Beginnings-Creating-the-Devblog-with-Jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve found myself with a strong desire to attempt game development. Not sure if it is something I will take seriously and follow through with, or if it is just another distraction that I find as a form of procrastination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what to do with my life, and at the moment this seems like something that could be helpful for me. I’ve never really blogged seriously before, I’ve set up many blogs in the past. None of them ever saw more than the initial post. Hopefully this is not another blog on a long list of unfinished projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blog needs to just be set up to work. I plan to take my time with the layout and styling. I don’t want an unfinished blog design to stop me from just writing the content and doing the things that I wish to do. I always have this idea that I need to prepare and setup everything perfectly as I want it to be before ever starting a project. And that is part of the problem for never having any finished projects, I never get around to finishing the setup, so I never get around to even starting them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So imperfect blog setup. Imperfect work. But finished, and active, that’s the hope for 2019. I stop not finishing a project or piece of art or anything. I follow through and finish.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Ohaeboy</name></author><summary type="html">I’ve found myself with a strong desire to attempt game development. Not sure if it is something I will take seriously and follow through with, or if it is just another distraction that I find as a form of procrastination.</summary></entry></feed>